http://harpsinc.org/terms-of-use/

Home >Terms of Use
In using this website you are deemed to have read and agreed to the following terms and conditions:
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions,
Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: “Client”,
“You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting
the Company’s terms and conditions. “The Company”, “Ourselves”, “We” and “Us”,
refers to our Company. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client
and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. All terms refer to the offer,
acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of
our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, whether by formal
meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of
meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services/products,
in accordance with and subject to, prevailing English Law. Any use of the above
terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or
he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to
same.
Privacy Statement
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized
employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information
collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data
to ensure the best possible service to our customers. Parliament has created
specific offences for unauthorised actions against computer systems and data.
We will investigate any such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking
civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible
Confidentiality
We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and as
such, any information concerning the Client and their respective Client Records
may be passed to third parties. However, Client records are regarded as
confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than
if legally required to do so to the
appropriate authorities. Clients have the right to request sight of, and copies
of any and all Client Records we keep, on the proviso that we are given
reasonable notice of such a request. Clients are requested to retain copies of
any literature issued in relation to the provision of our services. Where
appropriate, we shall issue Client’s with appropriate written information,
handouts or copies of records as part of an agreed contract, for the benefit of
both parties.
We will not sell, share, or rent your personal
information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail.
Any emails sent by this Company will only be in connection with the provision
of agreed services and products.
Disclaimer
Exclusions and Limitations
The information on this web site is provided on an “as is” basis. To the
fullest extent permitted by law, this Company:
excludes all representations and warranties relating to this website and its contents or which is or may be provided by any affiliates or any other third party, including in relation to any inaccuracies or omissions in this website and/or the Company’s literature; andexcludes all liability for damages arising out of or in connection with your use of this website. This includes, without limitation, direct loss, loss of
business or profits (whether or not the loss of such profits was
foreseeable, arose in the normal course of things or you have advised this
Company of the possibility of such potential loss), damage caused to your
computer, computer software, systems and programs and the data thereon or any other direct or indirect, consequential and incidental damages.
This Company does not however exclude liability for death or
personal injury caused by its negligence. The above exclusions and limitations
apply only to the extent permitted by law. None of your statutory rights as a
consumer are affected.
Payment
Returned cheques will incur a $25 charge to cover banking fees
and administrative costs. In an instance of a second Returned cheque, we
reserve the right to terminate the arrangement and, if agreed to, we shall
insist on future cash transactions only. Consequently, all bookings and/or
transactions and agreements entered into will cease with immediate effect until
such time as any and all outstanding monies are recovered in full.
Cancellation Policy
Minimum 24 hours notice of cancellation required. Notification
for instance, in person, via email, mobile phone ‘text message’ and/or fax, or
any other means will be accepted subject to confirmation in writing. We reserve
the right to levy a $30 charge to cover any subsequent administrative expenses.
Termination of Agreements and Refunds Policy
Both the Client and ourselves have the right to terminate any
Services Agreement for any reason, including the ending of services that are
already underway. No refunds shall be offered, where a Service is deemed to
have begun and is, for all intents and purposes, underway. Any monies that have
been paid to us which constitute payment in respect of the provision of unused
Services, shall be refunded.
Availability
Unless otherwise stated, the services featured on this website
are only available within the United States, or in relation to postings from
the United States. All advertising is intended solely for the United States
market. You are solely responsible for evaluating the fitness for a particular
purpose of any downloads, programs and text available through this site.
Redistribution or republication of any part of this site or its content is
prohibited, including such by framing or other similar or any other means,
without the express written consent of the Company. The Company does not
warrant that the service from this site will be uninterrupted, timely or error
free, although it is provided to the best ability. By using this service you
thereby indemnify this Company, its employees, agents and affiliates against
any loss or damage, in whatever manner, howsoever caused.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site,
track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate
use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and
troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access
information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and
referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used
only within this Company on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable
information related to this data will never be used in any way different to
that stated above without your explicit permission.
Cookies
Like most interactive web sites this Company’s website [or ISP]
uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are
used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and
ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also
use cookies.
Links to this website
You may not create a link to any page of this website without
our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website
you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above
will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.
Links from this website
We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s
websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material
appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and
should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be
aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of
these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site &
to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security
and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed
through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them.
This Company will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in
whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third
parties of personal information.
Copyright Notice
Copyright and other relevant intellectual property rights exists
on all text relating to the Company’s services and the full content of this
website.
This Company’s logo is a registered trademark of this Company in
the United States and other countries. The brand names and specific services of
this Company featured on this web site are trade marked.
Communication
We have several different e-mail addresses for different
queries. These, & other contact information, can be found on our Contact Us link
on our website or via Company literature or via the Company’s stated telephone,
facsimile or mobile telephone numbers.
Force Majeure
Neither party shall be liable to the other for any failure to
perform any obligation under any Agreement which is due to an event beyond the
control of such party including but not limited to any Act of God, terrorism,
war, Political insurgence, insurrection, riot, civil unrest, act of civil or
military authority, uprising, earthquake, flood or any other natural or man
made eventuality outside of our control, which causes the termination of an
agreement or contract entered into, nor which could have been reasonably
foreseen. Any Party affected by such event shall forthwith inform the other Party
of the same and shall use all reasonable endeavours to comply with the terms
and conditions of any Agreement contained herein.
Waiver
Failure of either Party to insist upon strict performance of any
provision of this or any Agreement or the failure of either Party to exercise
any right or remedy to which it, he or they are entitled hereunder shall not
constitute a waiver thereof and shall not cause a diminution of the obligations
under this or any Agreement. No waiver of any of the provisions of this or any
Agreement shall be effective unless it is expressly stated to be such and
signed by both Parties.
General
The laws of England and Wales govern these terms and conditions.
By accessing this website [and using our services/buying our products] you consent
to these terms and conditions and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English
courts in all disputes arising out of such access. If any of these terms are
deemed invalid or unenforceable for any reason (including, but not limited to
the exclusions and limitations set out above), then the invalid or
unenforceable provision will be severed from these terms and the remaining
terms will continue to apply. Failure of the Company to enforce any of the
provisions set out in these Terms and Conditions and any Agreement, or failure
to exercise any option to terminate, shall not be construed as waiver of such
provisions and shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions or
of any Agreement or any part thereof, or the right thereafter to enforce each and
every provision. These Terms and Conditions shall not be amended, modified,
varied or supplemented except in writing and signed by duly authorised
representatives of the Company.
Notification of Changes
The Company reserves the right to change these conditions from
time to time as it sees fit and your continued use of the site will signify
your acceptance of any adjustment to these terms. If there are any changes to
our privacy policy, we will announce that these changes have been made on our
home page and on other key pages on our site. If there are any changes in how
we use our site customers’ Personally Identifiable Information, notification by
e-mail or postal mail will be made to those affected by this change. Any
changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our web site 30 days prior to
these changes taking place. You are therefore advised to re-read this statement
on a regular basis
These terms and conditions form part of the
Agreement between the Client and ourselves. Your accessing of this website
and/or undertaking of a booking or Agreement indicates your understanding,
agreement to and acceptance, of the Disclaimer Notice and the full Terms and
Conditions contained herein. Your statutory Consumer Rights are unaffected.
Comments are closed.
